<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Food</string>
    <string name="app_bar_name">22 Best Dishes Around The World</string>
    <string name="food_name_1">1. Sushi, Japan</string>
    <string name="food_name_2">2. Rendang, Indonesia</string>
    <string name="food_name_3">3. Ramen, Japan</string>
    <string name="food_name_4">4. Tom Yam Goong, Thailand</string>
    <string name="food_name_5">5. Kebab, Turkey</string>
    <string name="food_name_6">6. Pho, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="food_name_7">7. Peking duck, China</string>
    <string name="food_name_8">8. Paella, Spain</string>
    <string name="food_name_9">9. Steak and Kidney Pie, England</string>
    <string name="food_name_10">10. Apfelstrudel, Austria</string>
    <string name="food_name_11">11. Pad Thai, Thailand</string>
    <string name="food_name_12">12. Goulash, Hungary</string>
    <string name="food_name_13">13. Lasagna, Italy</string>
    <string name="food_name_14">14. Kimchi, Korea</string>
    <string name="food_name_15">15. Fried chicken, United States</string>
    <string name="food_name_16">16. Dosa, India</string>
    <string name="food_name_17">17. Massaman Curry, Thailand</string>
    <string name="food_name_18">18. Pizza, Italy</string>
    <string name="food_name_19">19. Hamburger, Germany</string>
    <string name="food_name_20">20. Donuts, USA</string>
    <string name="food_name_21">21. Biryani, India</string>
    <string name="food_name_22">22. Poutine, Canada</string>
    <string name="food_description_1">Prepared with vinegared rice and a wide range of ingredients including seafood, vegetables, and sometimes fruits. Sushi tastes best when served with wasabi, pickled ginger, and soy sauce. A popular garnish for this dish is Daikon radish. The type of fish in it defines a sushis taste.</string>
    <string name="food_description_2">Rendang is prepared by simmering beef with coconut milk with a mixture of the best of spices including turmeric, garlic, lemongrass, ginger, chillies, and galangal. The dish is then stewed for a few hours which gives it a tender texture and exotic taste. </string>
    <string name="food_description_3">Ramen is a Japanese dish made of wheat noodles and served in the broth along with vegetables and meat. Ramen comes in several flavours, from tangy to spicy, depending on the flavour of the broth.</string>
    <string name="food_description_4">A type of sour and hot Thai soup, Tom yam goong is prepared with shrimp along with a load of healthy herbs and spices?  lemongrass, lime, kaffir leaves, galangal, and red chili peppers to name a few. the soup plays around with a bit of all possible flavours? spicy, sour, salty and sweet.</string>
    <string name="food_description_5">Kebabs are originally from Turkey. They consist of ground meat or seafood, fruits, and vegetables in some cases and are cooked on a skewer with a big fire underneath, just like a barbeque on the grill. It is cooked with various accompanying ingredients including garlic, black pepper, and vegetable oil. Mutton or lambs are generally the traditional meats used in kebabs.</string>
    <string name="food_description_6">Pho (pronounced as fuh) is a Vietnamese dish made of rice noodles and meat (usually beef or chicken) served in broth and topped with herbs. The dish has got a great fragrance which lingers in the eaters head for a while. A popular street food item.</string>
    <string name="food_description_7">Peking duck is a dish that finds its way to Beijing. The ducks for this dish are specially bred and slaughtered after 60 days and seasoned first before being roasted in closed ovens. This gives the meat a crisp skin and thin texture. The dish is served with cucumbers, spring onion, and sweet bean sauce. </string>
    <string name="food_description_8">Paella has got its roots in Valencia, Spain. It is an ancient dish recreated with a modern touch in the present times. There are various ways to eat Paella. The original recipe contains white rice with green beans, meat butterbeans, snails, topped with seasoning such as rosemary.</string>
    <string name="food_description_9">Steak and kidney pie is a piquant pie filled with diced beef, kidney (often of lamb, beef, or pork), brown gravy, and fried onion. It is a representative dish of British cuisine and culture. The gravy is made up of ale, flavoured beef broth, and cornstarch.</string>
    <string name="food_description_10">Apfelstrudel is a popular pastry in Austria and other parts of Europe. The dish consists of an oval strudel pastry cover with mouthwatering apple filling inside. The apple filling is prepared with grated apples, cinnamon, sugar, breadcrumbs, and raisins.</string>
    <string name="food_description_11">Pad Thai is a stir-fried rice dish accompanied with noodles. This healthy dish is made with stir-frying noodles with eggs and tofu. What brings out the flavour from the dish is the unique blend of sauces - tamarind pulp, dried shrimp and fish sauce and garnished with garlic and red chillii pepper. </string>
    <string name="food_description_12">Goulash is stew meat dating back to 9th century Hungary. The main elements of the dish are the spices, especially paprika. Goulash is prepared from either beef, pork, veal, or lamb. The meat is cut into pieces and neatly seasoned with salt. It is then browned with oil and sliced onion.</string>
    <string name="food_description_13">Italy lasagna takes over Pizza to be added in the worlds best food dishes list because of its comeback. It is one of the oldest pasta but has become popular only in the present times. The ingredients itself sound mouthwatering - meats, pasta, vegetables, tomato sauce, and lots and lots of cheese.</string>
    <string name="food_description_14">Kimchi is a staple Korean side dish prepared from fermented vegetables such as Korean radishes, and cabbage and topped with several seasonings, including garlic, chilli powder, scallions, and ginger. There is a huge variety of Kimchis made with different ingredients are is sold practically for free as starters in most restaurants in Korea. </string>
    <string name="food_description_15">Crunchy on the outside and juicy within, fried chicken, as the name suggests, is a dish consisting of chicken pieces deeply fried, giving it a crisp coating. The chicken is then seasoned with herbs and spices. The spicier, the better. Excess flour is used to make the crust thicker.</string>
    <string name="food_description_16">India has a lot to contribute when it comes to cuisine and dosa is the best dish to represent that. To put it in simple terms, dosa is a type of pancake made from fermented rice batter. The dish looks like a crepe and the main ingredients are black gram and rice. Earlier, Dosa was prominent only in South India and Sri Lanka. It is now a well-known dish in India and all over the world. </string>
    <string name="food_description_17"> Massaman curry is a mild, relatively rich curry of Thailand. Blended with the local spices, this tangy and not too spicy curry differs from the other regular curries of the nation and for all the right reasons. </string>
    <string name="food_description_18">This Italian Dish consists of a usually round, wheat base dough that is garnished with tomatoes, cheese, and often various other ingredients baked at a high temperature, traditionally in a wood-fired oven. </string>
    <string name="food_description_19">This popular dish of Germany consists of one or more cooked patties of ground meat, usually beef, that is placed right inside the sliced bread or a bun. This is then either pan-fried, grilled or smoked. Hamburgers are often served with lettuce, loads of cheese, tomato, pickles and whatnot.</string>
    <string name="food_description_20">The doughnut is popular in many countries and is prepared in various forms as a sweet snack. Donuts are usually deep-fried from a flour dough, and typically ring-shaped. Various toppings such as sugar.</string>
    <string name="food_description_21">This mixed rice dish has its origins amidst the Muslims of the Indian subcontinent. It is prepared by mixing a curry, later combining it with semi-cooked rice separately. This dish is especially popular throughout the Indian subcontinent, as well as among the diaspora from the region. </string>
    <string name="food_description_22">All the french-fries lovers in the house, this Canadian dish is what you need to get your hands on. Poutine includes french fries and cheese curds topped with traditional brown chicken gravy. Originated in the late 1950s in the central province of Canada, the hot gravy is usually served at room temperatures and t maintain the texture, the fries are added right before serving the dish. </string>
    <string name="about">About :-</string>
    <string name="expand_button_content_description">See more or less information about a food.</string>
</resources>